CONTACT

(L)

+250784860836



jeanndo.dev@gmail.com



https://github.com/Jeanndo



https://linkedin.com/in/ukwitegetse



Kigali-Rwanda

HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Antd
- Mui
- Figma
- Tailwind
- Leaflet
- Javascript
- Typescript
- React
- Next js
- Node
- PayPal Node js
- Express
- GraphQL
- REST API
- MongoDB
- PostgresSql
- Firebase/firestore
- Paython (Basics)
- C
- C++
- Java

JEAN DE DIEU UKWITEGETSE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Jean De Dieu UKWITEGETSE is a full stack developer by professional with 3 years of experience. He is passionate about expending his horizons to projects that needs development support and consultancy. And he is capable of working in a team or in any environment as well as eager to learn new skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer Trainee at Andela Mar 2022- Jun 2022

As a full stack developer at Andela he worked on the following tasks:

Frontend:

- · Landing Page Design
- Dashboard pages Design.
- API integration
- Bus motion simulation on leaflet map
- · Leading Frontend developers
- writing Tests
- Frontend Code Reviews

Backend:

- · Backend project setup
- Writing RESTFUL APIs with Node Js, Express, Sequelize and PostgresSql for Database
- · Testing APIs with Postman
- · Writing Tests for RESTFUL APIs
- Writing Documentation For RESTFUL APIs
- Backend Code Reviews
- Leading Backend Developers
- Deploying Backend Project on Heroku Platform

Backend Developer at HAZA TECH

Mar 2019 - Jan 2020

Tasks:

- Writing RESTFUL APIs with NODE JS, EXPRESS, and MongoDB for Database.
- Testing RESTFUL APIs with Postman
- Writing Test for RESTFUL APIs with Jest
- · Writing Documentation for RESTFUL APIS with Swagger
- Leading Team of three Backend Developers
- · Assigning Tasks to team Members
- Backend Code Reviews
- Deploying Backend Project on Heroku Platform.

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication skills
- Time management
- Flexibility
- Motivation
- · Decision making
- Multitasking
- Problem solving

LANGUAGE

- English
- Kinyarwanda

Frontend Developer at Panel Tech

Mar 2021 - July 2021

Tasks:

- Design implementation with React, and Mui for three websites
- Dashboard Design
- API integration.
- Code Review
- Project Management
- Deploying Website on Digital Ocean

ACHIEVEMENTS

2020 Built and deployed my first e-commerce website.

Link:

https://www.fhousestore.com

2021 Worked and deployed three team project for Akagera-Rhein-Center

Links:

https://www.akagera-rhein-aupair.org

https://www.akagera-rhein-academy.com

https://www.akagera-rhein-center.org

2019 Built an Android mobile app for Academic Transcript requesting using Java

Link for GitHub repo:

https://www.github.com/Jeanndo/Transcript

EDUCATION

University of Rwanda 2017 - 2022

Bachelor's Degree in Computer and Software Engineering.